[{"answer": "I think it may happen someday.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "You want to be a Brit, really, don't you?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "You know, I see why this is not a great story for the president, because Kamala Harris is a brainy, up and coming politician and it is a little strange that her national introduction to the political stage is a discussion about whether or not it was OK for the president to call her pretty or not.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Jodi, are you as offended as everybody else seems to be the president called an attorney general the best-looking in the country?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "It's not the same.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Would you feel equally affronted?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Different people in different situations.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "No, because that's not a barrier to men participating in the work force.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "If he told lower ranking employees in his administration, for example, that they were good-looking but they happened to be men, would you feel that that was equally offensive?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I don't think it is.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "I mean, there's feminism and there's feminism and then there's nonsense, isn't there?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "HAIT: She needs and deserves to be judged on her merits and her qualifications, not to be --", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "That's a disgrace?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "I don't -- look, (a), I've got 90 percent female staff.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "But, Piers, would you walk into an editorial meeting for your program and say to a female producer in front of everybody else, you look fantastic today?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "No, you're a very handsome man and that's completely out of bounds.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "But who cares?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "-- we maybe parsing an even smaller matter, Piers, because this is literally one word out of place which is significant in part only because Michelle Obama is so careful in everything she says that it's very rare to hear her make any kind of gaffe whatsoever.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Jodi?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "No, I would attach zero significance to that.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Jonathan, do you find it another disgraceful incident?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I'm fine.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Senator Mitchell, how are you?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Well, we are obligated by treaty, of course, with South Korea to defend if there is an attack upon South Korea.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "I mean, can you see a scenario where America would have to do something?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "It's pretty hard to improve upon Theodore Roosevelt's statement that you should walk softly and carry a big stick.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "What is the more -- what is the consistent strategy you think that's most effective?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Uncle Jeremy?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Are you going to have a beard in the \"Entourage\" movie?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "You'll always be Ari.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "And can you watch your language please?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Well, you know what's funny is I -- is I came up with that sketch and, I just thought it was a really fun way to -- just to kind of send up the whole, you know, preconceived notion of it all, because, you know, before I had done that role, there was no reference to me being anyway near or like that character.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "How do you get away, even from your closest nearest and dearest, from being the great Ari Gold?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "I wanted you to -- I said, my exact words to you were, can you treat me like Lloyd?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I -- I have met him, yes.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Have you met him?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Well, I -- no, he certainly was not enraged.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Was he flattered or enraged?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "I mean, can I tell a story?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "What -- did you -- did you see the end of the \"Funny Or Die\" clip?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Right in the front of the store.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Where will it be, Mr. Selfridge?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "It -- well, I have no idea, because you know what's interesting is when I met with the producers for \"Mr. Selfridge,\" I said, Harry is from Chicago and there's a very hard Chicago accent.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "How bad is it?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "IVEN: I -- I do.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Do you go along with that?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Is it going to happen, do you think?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I -- you know, I feel like I'm the last to know, if that makes any sense.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "I don't know, but do you know?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Can you give me a flicker of hope?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Can he?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "How much is Hollywood to blame in terms of the culture, the system, the way it builds up big stars and then maybe leaves them alone when they're on the skids?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Well -- I mean, definitely surround yourself with great people.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "What would you say to them?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "You know, it's been incredible how everything has shifted just I would say in the last year.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "What do you make of the way the debate's gone?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Oh, definitely.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Would you like to get married yourself?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Well, originally, the director and I just set out to go find one of the world's last undiscovered waves.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "What was the original purpose of this film?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "Well, Geoff and I were friends and I knew he had quite a few projects on the go as a producer, reality-based, and some in the spirits world.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "But how did you hear about this and what prompted you to get involved?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "The size of it, I think, is difficult to determine and less important than the fact that there is a definite civil and political conflict there that needs attention.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Are we talking about another Rwanda happening that we're just not really covering much?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "Well, I think one of the things that we're going to try to do, which a lot of filmmakers that have low budgets try to do is really engage the community.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "So how are you going to get this hyped enough to really make a difference, do you think?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "Not -- not necessarily.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Are you concerned about treading into the political arena like this?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I think we all, you know, the -- the human condition should be put at the fore because I think there's a ripple effect.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "What do you say to them?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130405pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "Are you ready to get on the computers?", "qSentId": 727}]